yangonlife.com.mm 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Yangon Life

YANGON LIFE - Privacy Statement

YANGON LIFE is committed to protecting your privacy and personal information when you deal with us.

We will only use personal information provided by you for the purposes for which it was required.

We will disclose to a third party when it is required to facilitate a service you have requested; and when law requires it or to prevent or investigate suspected unlawful activity.

We have implemented security technology and procedures, rules and measures to protect the personal information under our control against: unauthorised access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss.

We will remove personal information from our systems where it is no longer required (except where archiving is required).

YANGON LIFE - Privacy Policy

By using our website, you agree to this Policy.

This website may use Cookies, Web Beacons, and/or other similar types of technologies.

  * A Cookie is a small piece of text that is stored by your web browser, and is often used to store your preferences for a specific website.
  * A Web Beacon is a clear, very tiny image (1x1 pixel), and it helps us and our advertising partners understand how you use our site.

The purpose for using these technology is to enable YANGON LIFE monitor community preferences to help focus our future developments of the website in the areas of most interest to our users; and to provide information to advertisers to help them understand the level of interest in their advertisements from our user community.

We and our advertising partners use both of these technologies to help deliver more relevant advertisements about products and services that interest you. These technologies do not store any personal information about you, (e.g. your name, phone number, address, or email address).
